123world.com 2003-04-01

# Privacy Policy - 123World

**123World takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers 123World's treatment of personally identifiable information that 123World collects when you are on the 123World site, and when you use 123World's services. This policy also covers 123World's treatment of any personally identifiable information that 123World's business partners share with 123World. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 123World does not own or control, or to people that 123World does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection & Use**

  * 123World collects personally identifiable information when you register for a 123World account, when you use certain 123World products or services, when you visit 123World pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. 123World may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
  * When you register with 123World, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with 123World and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * 123World also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, 123World cookie information and the page you requested.
  * 123World uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

**Information Sharing & Disclosure**

  * 123World will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * 123World will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:   

    * We have your consent to share the information;   

    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  

    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of 123World to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);   

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the 123World Surfing Agreement, the or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**

  * 123World may set and access 123World cookies on your computer.
  * 123World allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to 123World's cookies. 
  * 123World uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with 123World products and services.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

  * 123World may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
